arts.gov 2018-12-29

# Privacy Policy | NEA

Thank you for visiting the National Endowment for the Arts Website and reviewing our privacy  
policy. Our privacy policy is clear: We will collect **no** personal information about  
you when you visit our website unless you choose to provide that information to us.

### Cookies

We do not use "persistent" web cookies. Persistent web cookies are defined as web cookies that can track "the activities of users over time and across different web sites.

Session cookies, the kind used on this site, automatically expire when users leave a site. Session cookies retain information only during the session or for the purpose of completing a particular online transaction, without any capacity to track users over time and across different web sites.

### Emails and Web Forms

Personally identifying information that you provide by email and/or web forms will be used only for  
such purposes as are described at the point of collection (for example on a web form), such as to  
send information or products to you, process your application, or to respond to your questions or comments. If you provide contact information, NEA staff or its contractors may contact you to clarify your comment or question, or to learn about your level of customer satisfaction with our services. We do not sell any personal information to third parties.

Comments sent to NEA blogs are processed by the Mollom anti-spam service to prevent spam submissions. Further details on their privacy policy can be seen at <http://mollom.com/web-service-privacy-policy>.

### Information Collected and Stored Automatically

If you do nothing during your visit but browse through the web site, read pages, or  
download information, we will gather and store certain information about your visit  
automatically. This information does not identify you personally. We automatically collect  
and store only the following information about your visit:

  1. The Internet domain (for example, "xcompany.com" if you use a private Internet access  
account, or "your school.edu" if you connect from a university) and IP address (an IP  
address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are  
surfing the Web) from which you access our web site;
  2. The type of browser and operating system used to access our site;
  3. The date and time you access our site;
  4. The pages you visit and how long you visited each page; and
  5. If you linked to the NEA web site from another web site, the address of  
that web site.

We use this information to help us make our site more useful to visitors and to learn  
about the number of visitors to our site and the types of technology our visitors use. We  
do not track or record information about individuals and their visits.

### Links to Other Sites

Our policy discloses the privacy practices for the NEA web site. But NEA provides links to  
other web sites. When you leave the NEA web site ([www.arts.gov](http://www.arts.gov/)), you will go to  
sites outside our control. These external sites may send their own  
cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. The privacy policies and  
procedures described here for NEA do not apply to any external links. We encourage you to  
read the privacy policies of any site you link to from ours, especially if you share any  
personal information. Be informed. You are the person best qualified to protect your own  
privacy.

### Security

For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users,  
the National Endowment for the Arts uses software programs to monitor network traffic to identify  
unauthorized attempts to upload or change information or otherwise cause damage.

Unauthorized attempts to upload information or change information on this service are  
strictly prohibited and may be punishable under the Computer Fraud and Abuse Act of 1986  
and 18 U.S.C. Sec. 1001 and 1030. Information also may be used for authorized law  
enforcement investigations. Except for the above purposes, no other attempts are made to  
identify individual users or their usage habits.
